swipesapp.com 2014-12-22

# !

Privacy Policy
!
We at Swipes Incorporated regard your privacy and right to confidentiality of data as very
important. Your data is collected and used in accordance to the relevant provisions of the
American data protection legislation. In this Privacy Policy, we are informing you which of
your data we collect and for what purposes. The policy regards information disclosed by
the users of the website: http://swipesapp.com, of the mobile and web Swipes apps.
!
Controller
!
Swipes is a global service. However, by accessing the app, you consent to the processing
of your data in the United States as the Service is operated from the United States. Your
data is protected by the laws of United States of America. If you have any questions or
concerns about data protection, you are welcome to contact us by email at this address:
support@swipesapp.com or mail us at:
!
Swipes Incorporated
16192 Coastal Highway, Lewes
Delaware, 19958
United States of America
!
Subject of data protection
!
The subject of data protection is personal and non-personal identification information. We
may collect personal details such as your name, your email address, and the use-data that
you have provided in various ways - subscription on the website, to a newsletter,
registration to the mobile, tablet and web apps or respond to a survey, in connection to our
products and services. We will ask you for appropriate name and email address but the
submission of data is voluntarily. You can always refuse to supply personal identification
information, however that may prevent you from engaging in certain website and/or app
related activities.
!
Automatically collected data
!
For statistical purposes, we may also collect non-personal identification information about
your interaction with our website and the Swipes iOS and web apps. The internet browser is
automatically transmitting information about your IP (Internet Protocol) address, IMEI
number, location, usage analytics, type of browser and version, language, cookies, session
records and the time and date you accessed the Services.
Also App Store is automatically transmitting data among which is but not only - device of
use, location and operational system.
This data is not assigned to an identifiable person and is stored separately from personal
data.
Data entered by the users
You can use the Swipes products with a registration via email and password or with a
Facebook registration. The data of each registered user is constantly backed-up to the
Cloud and accessible on all Swipes platforms, if and when, the user has an internet
coverage on the device that he/she uses to make the content changes in Swipes with.
                                 Privacy Policy - Swipes Incorporated

You can use the Swipes iOS app without any registration by choosing the logging option
“Try Swipes”. The data entered by an unregistered users is not backed-up in the cloud. The
data is stored locally on the device that the user uses to access the Swipes platform from.
An unregistered user will not be able to restore data in case of lost. The entered data is not
associated to any account and it cannot be accessed on another Swipes product than the
one used for creating it.
In case of registration, we use your email data as a contact reference. We send newsletters
around each update and you can unsubscribe from them at any point. The email
information allows us to be able to respond to your wishes, questions and criticism.
You can access Swipes on iPhone, iPod, iPad devices, as well as on a an internet browser
through the Swipes Web app. The use of the app on any device is free of charge as well as
the synchronisation between the diﬀerent platforms we support.
The premium upgrade of Swipes - Swipes Plus has been discontinued on July 2, 2014. We
no longer support upgrades. However, the users who had an active monthly or yearly
subscription to Swipes Plus by July 2, 2014, will remain having access to the location-based
reminders on their iOS Swipes app.
To activate the location-based reminders, you need to allow permission to Swipes to access
your location coordinates. You can always deny this access, however that will prevent you
from using the service.
If you were not a Swipes Plus user who had been given the option to use the location
reminders, we do not ask you for access and we do not track your location information from
your iOS device at any time.
Transfer of data
Your data will not be transferred to third parties without asking for your consent in advance.
Data transfer to third parties without informing you separately beforehand can occur in the
following exceptional cases as explained below:
   • In case of legal investigation of Swipes Incorporated, personal data will be transferred
      to the criminal investigation authorities and, if appropriate, to injured third parties. We
      will only do this if there are concrete indications of illegal and/or abusive behavior.
   • We also depend on the use of external service providers to supply us services for
      processing and/or storing data, customer service, advertising and in the future -
      processing payments. In this cases, information is transferred to the suppliers to
      enable the services. However, we select the providers carefully for their transparency
      of privacy.
   • Swipes Incorporated may go through a change of legal form. We may also form, sell or
      buy subsidiaries, divisions or parts of the company. In such transactions, the user
      information together with the part of the company to be transferred, will be passed on.
      This processes will be done in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the relevant
      data protection laws.
!
!
                                   Privacy Policy - Swipes Incorporated

Policy regarding children
The Swipes services are NOT intended for children under the age of 18. Swipes does not
knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 18 and believes
that minors should get their parents' consent before giving out any personal information. If
there is any case of a child disclosing personal information, we expect the parents or
guardians to contact us and request the deletion of it.
Changes in your data
If you want to delete your account, please inform us at support@swipesapp.com. We will be
grateful to hear your reasons for leaving us, so that we can constantly improve the service.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security
measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of
your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on
our servers.
To ensure the secure transfer of your data when synchronizing and backing-up, we’re using
the trusted infrastructure of Amazon Web Services. You can read further on their security
processes on: http://media.amazonwebservices.com/pdf/AWS_Security_Whitepaper.pdf
Sensitive and private data exchange between the website/the mobile app/the web app and
its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and
protected with digital signatures.
Changes to this privacy policy
Swipes reserves the right to alter the Privacy Policy at any time. When we do that, we will
revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently
check this page for any changes. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility
to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using our website - http://swipesapp.com and the Swipes mobile, tablet and web apps,
you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy, as well as our Terms and Conditions:
http://swipesapp.com/termsofuse.pdf. If you do not agree to these policies, please do not
use our products and services.
This document was last updated on June 24, 2014.
                                Privacy Policy - Swipes Incorporated
